## RESUME

## SOCIAL

- xing.com/profile/Augusto\_Juvenal
- linkedin.com/in/augusto-giles-801a9654
- Skype auguastogiles

## LANGUAGES

Portuguese - Native speaking

English - Fluent speaking

## EDUCATION

JAN 2010 - JUL 2016

#### Bachelor's in computer science

Federal University of Pernambuco - BR

# PROJECTS

re-wine.netlify.com wecolab-homolog.netlify.com github.com/augustogiles

## CERTIFICATIONS

#### PSM I

Scrum.org

# FCE - BI

Cambridge Language Assessment

# SKILLS

Javascript
Java

**Professional Skills :** POO, Spring, Express, API RESTful, Git, Docker, Scrum Methodology, Elasticsearch, SQL, NoSQL, Kafka, JIRA

# **Augusto Costa**

WEB DEVELOPER

Phone: (351) 912 244 722, | Email: augustogiles@gmail.com

## ABOUT ME

I'm 28 years old Brazilian Web Developer & Freelance currently based in Lisbon. I love everything that has to do with programming and new technologies. Despite my Java background, since 2018 I started to work with ReactJS because I decided to consolidate my career as a frontend developer.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

SINCE JUN 2019

#### **Full Stack Developer**

PDMFC, Lisbon - PT

- Started to implement and maintain Scrum in the team (dealing with Scrum team to show the benefits of the Scrum in the project.)
- Main responsible by the invoice feature (integrating with Moloni) and by the flow that generates card's certificates (PKI);
- Customer Service (production environment) to help and identify bugs and improvements between the incremental process;

Technologies: ReactJS, Java (Eclipselink), SQLServer, PKI, Git, Docker, Scrum.

MAY 2018 - FEB 2019

## **Senior Software Developer**

Mobix Software Studio, Pernambuco - BR

I was allocated (outsourcing) in a confidential project to build a platform for entrepreneurs and startups help and share information to each other (a social media like).

- **Technologies:** Microservices, Java (Spring), MongoDB, Elasticsearch, Git, Docker, Python, Flask, Kafka, Jenkins, Redis.

JUL 2016 - MAY 2018

### Security Analyst

Tempest Security Intelligence, Pernambuco - BR

- Automation of vulnerability tests;
- Infrastructure Security Consulting;

Technologies: Java, Ruby scripts, Shell Scripts, JIRA, Git

OCT 2014 - JUN 2016

#### Jr Backend Developer | Remote

E.Life, São Paulo - BR

- Developed solutions Java Web (Hibernate) responsible to retrieve information from social media and feed the company product;
- Developed features to centralize all social networks in an application (ETL). Thus, the user can manage your accounts and spread your posts, actions and do a better customer support for their clients;

**Technologies:** Java (Hibernate); Ruby scripts, Twitter API, Facebook API, SQL database